<resources>

    <!-- issue_create_account -->
    <string name="issue_create_account_title">Create new account</string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_name_label">Account name - characters (A&#8211;Z) digits (1&#8211;5)</string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_name_hint">Account name</string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_instructions_label">
        Resources are required to create an account on the EOS blockchain, as such there is a small cost
        to create an account. We will generate a local private key, create an account, and assign
        your public key as its owner. Your private key is RSA encrypted using a key stored in the AndroidKeyStore,
        it will never leave this device.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_private_key_instruction_title_label">Your account has been created.</string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_private_key_instruction_label">
        The private key below was added as both the active and owner permission
        of your new account. Please backup this private key somewhere in the physical world and avoid storing it
        digitally.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_create_button">Create Account (%s)</string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_done_button">Done</string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_sku_error">
        Our create account feature is currently unavailable, you can still use this app by importing an
        existing private key.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_billing_setup_error">
        We could not connect to Google play, please check your internet connection and try again.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_billing_purchase_cancelled_error">
        You cancelled the Google play purchase, you can alternatively import an existing private key
        if you do not want to pay our fee.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_billing_purchase_item_unavailable_error">
        Our account issuing service is currently frozen. You can use the app by importing an existing
        private key, we apologies for any inconvenience.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_billing_purchase_failed_error">
        Google play could not process your payment, please check your internet connection and try again.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_billing_purchase_fatal_error">
        You have already purchased an account, but unfortunately an issue occurred while processing your transaction.
        You will have received an email confirmation containing your purchaseId, please contact support@memtrip.com quoting
        this purchaseId. We will resolve this for you ASAP.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_username_validation_error">
        Please enter an account name that is 12 characters in length.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_generic_error">
        We could not create an account at this time, please check your connection and try again.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_fatal_error">
        We could not create an account at this time, please check your connection and try again. If you
        continue to encounter difficulties, please contact support@memtrip.com and quote your purchase id.
        A list of your purchase ids can be found in settings -> transaction history.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_account_name_exists">
        The account name you chose already exists, please choose another name.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_import_key_error_title">Could not import key</string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_import_key_error_body">
        We could not import private key, please check your internet connection and try again. If you
        continue to encounter difficulties, please clear your app data and import the private key that
        you just backed up.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_create_account_import_key_no_accounts">
        We could not find your recently created account, it can take some time for these changes to propagate through
        the EOS network. Please wait a few minutes and try again. If you continue to encounter difficulties, please
        change the EOS endpoint URL in settings and import the private key that you just backed up.
    </string>

    <!-- issue_import_key -->
    <string name="issue_import_key_toolbar_title">Import existing key</string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_instructions">
        The private key you enter will be RSA encrypted, it will never leave this device. If you
        have trust issues (we don\'t blame you), build this app from source.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_github_url_button">View source on github</string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_github_source_url">https://github.com/memtrip/eosreach</string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_private_key_hint">Private key</string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_import">Import</string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_error_generic">Could not import private key, please check your connection and try again.</string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_error_invalid_private_key_format">Invalid private key format.</string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_error_no_accounts">
        We did not find any accounts associated with this private key, the Create Account option is the
        easiest way to get started. If this is unexpected, try changing the EOS endpoint in settings.
    </string>
    <string name="issue_import_key_private_key_already_imported">
        You have already imported this private key, sync your accounts to update the details for this key.
    </string>

</resources>
